<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<file.v.train><file.v.1>§ Request an amendment to your health record if you believe that something in your record is incorrect or incomplete. Your request must be in writing and HMAA has the right to deny your request. If we do deny your request, you have the right to file a statement that you disagree with us. Your statement will be added to your record.</file.v.1><file.v.2>§ File a complaint if you feel your privacy rights have been violated. You may file a complaint with the HMAA Privacy Officer, or you may file a complaint with the Secretary of the United States Department of Health and Human Services. Federal law prevents any retaliation to filed complaints.</file.v.2><file.v.3>If you failed to filed a tax return with the IRS, you can still file late your return and begin to rectify the situation now. Don't worry; you aren't the only one in this predicament, but if you don't take action soon the IRS could be calling you, and even garnishing your wages.</file.v.3><file.v.4>All taxpayers are encouraged to file their tax returns on time and to pay their taxes in full, if possible. If your taxes are going to be due now, you should still take your return, file late, and attempt to pay the taxes on a payment plan. The worst possible case is neglecting to file a</file.v.4><file.v.5>Big Brother is very vigilant when it comes to collecting taxes that are due. Not only can unfilled tax forms and unpaid taxes mean garnishment of wages, it can also result in your bank accounts and other assets being scooped up by the government. There is even a Federal Tax Lien that can be filed that will effectively destroy your credit and businesses. You should file any and all late tax returns now and this will stop any more penalties and interest from accruing.</file.v.5><file.v.6>If you should have filed a tax return for last year or a prior year but didn't, you should file the return as soon as possible, to claim a refund or pay the tax you owe and avoid the interest that accrues. You can obtain the forms and information you need from the IRS.</file.v.6><file.v.7>The IRS has clarified this criteria. A taxpayer may claim a dependent as a qualifying relative. A dependent will not be considered a qualifying child of another taxpayer if that dependent's "parent or (or other person with respect to whom the individual is defined as a qualifying child) is not required ... to file an income tax return and (i) does not file an income tax return, or (ii) files an income tax return solely to obtain a refund of withheld income taxes." Source: Notice 2008-5 (pdf). While this may make it easier for you to claim a qualifying relative, it will be more important than ever to be diligent in making sure that you can claim the dependent.</file.v.7><file.v.8>Murder Charges Filed in Iraq Soldier Shooting A U.S. Army sergeant who was due to leave Iraq soon after multiple tours has been charged with murder in the fatal shooting o... A U.S. Army sergeant who was due to leave Iraq soon after multiple tours has been charged with murder in the fatal shooting of five fellow soldiers at a U.S. military counseling... </file.v.8><file.v.9>Passengers File Lawsuit Over Jet Crash Two passengers on the Continental Airlines jet that veered off a Denver runway last month have filed lawsuits. The passengers... Two passengers on the Continental Airlines jet that veered off a Denver runway last month have filed lawsuits. The passengers claim in their suit that the pilot negligently...</file.v.9><file.v.10>This is a story about a tenant who defaulted on a lease; how I sued for $125.83 plus costs; how she filed a counterclaim, lied in court and won and how I appealed. For this suit, I was representing one of my corporations as an individual, and the opposing attorney filed a motion saying I was practicing law without a license, and proceeded to quote the Pennsylvania Rule of Civil Procedure that stated that an individual couldn't legally represent a corporation. Yes, the rule specifically states that a corporation must be represented by a lawyer, must sue and be sued in the name of the corporation.</file.v.10><file.v.11>I approached his bench with my executed assignment of lease in hand. Raymond Como, President was the grantor of the assignment and Raymond Como, Individual was the grantee. It was all properly executed and done at arms length. He took it, looked at it; looked at me and the opposing attorney and said "Dismissed. Start over. Mr. Como, you have twenty days to file an amended complaint clarifying this." Guess what? The defendant, my opponent has already paid over $400 in legal fees and I enjoyed attending this court room class for the small cost of my filing fees.</file.v.11><file.v.12>Increasingly, North Carolina taxpayers are choosing a faster, more convenient way to file their State and Federal income tax returns called electronic filing or E-Filing. In 2008, two out of every three North Carolina taxpayers E-Filed their individual income tax returns. This is a 14.28% increase over last year, which means the Department processed over 2.5 million individual income tax returns received through our safe and secure E-File program.</file.v.12><file.v.13>If you would like a tax professional to electronically file your Federal and State returns, the Department maintains a list of tax professionals that offer electronic filing. Select Locating a Tax Professional in Your Area. You will be asked to provide your zip code to receive a list of tax professionals in your area.</file.v.13><file.v.14>A true uncontested divorce is where one party files and the other party never files an answer and the party who files obtains a default judgment. In that sense, most cases are contested in some manner, whether it be property settlement, spousal support, custody, parenting time or child support. Although, in Washington, most cases settle before going to trial. See our Divorce page for more information.</file.v.14><file.v.15>If your spouse has properly filed a Summons and a Petitionfor Divorce, and you have been properly served, you must respond. If you choose to do nothing, your spouse can receive a Default Judgment of Divorce, awarding him/her everything he/she requests, by virtue of your failure to respond to the Court in writing. See our Divorce page for more details.</file.v.15><file.v.16>If you leave the home, your spouse may file a Motion for Temporary Orders stating that only he/she is entitled to stay in the home during the divorce proceedings, and that you cannot return to the home except to collect your personal belongings.</file.v.16><file.v.17>Generally, if there is no court order stating otherwise, and your spouse has only been gone a short time, the police will enforce his/her right to return to the home. Once you file for divorce, it may be possible to receive an order for exclusive occupancy under certain circumstances such as him having left the home or due to domestic violence issues. If you have been a victim of violence from your spouse or he/she has made violent threats, it may be possible to receive am Order for Protection from the court without filing for divorce. This type of order may include a provision that he/she is prohibited from appearing where you live.</file.v.17><file.v.18>Despite his imminent suspension from the practice of law, on or about July 20, 1998, Zablocki filed a Chapter 7 bankruptcy action on behalf of the couple. Although there was an obvious conflict of interest between Zablocki's representation of the wife against her husband in the divorce case and the representation of both the husband and wife in the bankruptcy case, Zablocki did not obtain the written consent of either the husband or wife to this arrangement. At no time did Zablocki notify the husband or wife of the fact that his license was to be suspended and that he would be unable to act as their attorney after that date. He also did not notify the bankruptcy trustee, bankruptcy court, or circuit court before which the divorce case was pending of his suspension and inability to act after Aug. 10, 1998. Zablocki did not refund any portion of the fee the couple had paid him for the bankruptcy action.</file.v.18><file.v.19>Question: How can my ex-husband file court papers changing the custody orders made with our divorce, stating that i can not take my son out of the county they live in. hes not even his son. its a long story and i need help getting my kids back.</file.v.19><file.v.20>Service. Before a case is started, the defendant must be served with the papers which gives the defendant notice that a lawsuit has been filed. The Sheriff or a private process server will perform this function. A party or lawyer cannot serve lawsuits.</file.v.20><file.v.21>Automatic Injunctions. If your lawyer tells you the case has been filed and an automatic injunction was issued, in Tennessee this means a court has ordered that you cannot do certain things. Make sure you understand those things you cannot do. Examples include harassing your spouse, giving away money to your best friend, moving with your children to Alaska, or removing your spouse from your health insurance.</file.v.21><file.v.22>Pendente lite support. “Pendente lite” is a Latin phrase meaning: pending the litigation. If either party needs child support, alimony, or attorney’s fees while the case is pending, a “Motion for Pendente Lite Support” is filed. The hearing is heard before a “divorce referee.” The divorce referee is a lawyer no longer practicing family law chosen to determine the support on a more expedited basis. The ruling of the divorce referee can be appealed to the judge.</file.v.22><file.v.23>Discovery. At any time during the case, preferably at the beginning, a party may file pleadings asking for discovery to learn about certain facts. Interrogatories, Request for Production of Documents, Request for Admissions, and Depositions are all forms of discovery. Almost always, there should be discovery before trial. In most cases, it is best to review discovery before a settlement offer is proposed. Generally, a party must respond to filed discovery within thirty days.</file.v.23><file.v.24>Order. The court’s ruling on a motion or petition requiring the parties to do certain things or setting forth their rights and responsibilities. An order is reduced to writing, signed by the judge, and filed with the court.</file.v.24><file.v.25>Consent Order. An order agreed upon by opposing parties or attorneys. A consent order is also reduced to writing, signed by the judge, and filed with the court.</file.v.25><file.v.26>my wife has just filed a divorced petition and she ask me for some unresonable maintenance fee for her and the kids which is beyond my means. the lawyer told me that if i cannot agrre to her she will have to filed a contested petition. what should i do now ? do i need to look for a lawyer and what is the preceeding will be.</file.v.26><file.v.27>Before your wife can file a contested divorce petition, she has to refer the marriage to a marriage tribunal which will call both parties to appear before them for reconciliation purposes. If the tribunal is unable to reconcile both of you (there will be several meetings over a period of 4 - 6 months) it will issue a certificate stating as such. Your wife needs this certificate before she can file a contested divorce petition.</file.v.27><file.v.28>If she already has the certificate and can file immediately, then she will have to serve you with the divorce petition. At this stage you will need to see a lawyer immediately.</file.v.28><file.v.29>Civil suit filed Sept. 2002 alleged Gill molested a 14 yr old boy in 1977 in rectory and on trip to New Hampshire. Victim did not tell parents until 2002 and they then told the Diocese. Gill, who retired in 1998, was barred from public ministry at that time. Another man filed suit in June 2003 alleging abuse in 1975. Name appears on list of priests released by San Diego Diocese 3/07.</file.v.29><file.v.30>Suit filed against two other priests (Moorse and Tarlton) included allegation that Gillespie abused a boy on the grounds of St. John's Abbey in 1977 and 1978. He has been living on restrictions at St. John's Abbey. Per 7/13/08 posting, four former students have accused him of abuse between 1977-1987.</file.v.30><file.v.31>Man filed suit 6/03 claiming he was abused by Glynn for 3 yrs in early 1970s. Later article says two other allegations have surfaced since suit was filed. 4 other men filed suit 10/03. One said he told another priest in 1971. If action had been taken, the other 3 would not have been abused. Glynn was a Navy chaplain in WWII. He died 1993 at age 80. At least 1 claim included in 10/05 settlement with Archdiocese.</file.v.31><file.v.32>12 young men filed suits beginning 8/98 alleging that Goodman abused them (mostly in 1980s) and that at least twice Diocese officials were informed of the abuse but failed to take action. Other suits followed. Goodman "resigned" from parish in 1997. Settlement with 13 in 1999. Placed on perm. leave in 2002. Lawsuit filed 2005, dropped, and re-filed 1/06. This suit dismissed 6/07 as beyond SOL. Named in 4/07 lawsuit. This suit, with others, were dismissed on SOL in 2007 &amp; 2008. All may be reinstated 1/09.</file.v.32><file.v.33>In 1989 civil suit, man alleges that Goodrich fondled, kissed and bit him on church premises between 1974 and 1988. Settled 1990 for $446K. Goodrich retired in 1988 and later suffered a stroke that left him mentally incapacitated. He died in 1995. Atleast one additional suit filed 10/04. There are as many as 14 accusers against Goodrich.</file.v.33><file.v.34>Gorecki accused of molesting at least 2 youths over a period of several years. Civil suit filed 1995. By 1999 there were 5 plaintiffs in the suit. Settled 3/01. Other claims settled by Diocese as part of massive $20 mil settlement w/ 40 people in 10/03. One victim says Gorecki fondled him on several occasions. He finally told his mom; she complained to a nun at the school. Shortly thereafter, Gorecki was "gone." He spent some time outside the diocese and then was reassigned to different parishes.</file.v.34><file.v.35>Gormley admitted to molesting one youth in 1966 and other boys in the 1950s and 1960s. He took a leave of absence in 1969 and left priesthood 2 years later. Problems were know prior to ordination and he was in therapy for 30 yrs. In 1993 he apologized to 1966 victim after chance encounter. This man filed civil suit in 1993 and later settled for $70K.</file.v.35><file.v.36>Guerra was charged with being sexually involved with 14 yr old boy in 1981. Boy told his mother in 1983. Charges against Guerra were dropped in 1986 because law had changed in 1983 to require corroboration in cases that were not promptly filed.</file.v.36><file.v.37>Ordained in Ireland. Came to Los Angeles 1975. Became incardinated in Los Angeles 1988. Retired 6/02 after allegations known. Investigated by police re 1992 accusation of abuse of girls in 1970s. Named as abuser in massive suit filed 2003. Claims settled in July, 2007 when Arch. agreed to massive $660 mil settlement with over 500 plaintiffs.</file.v.37><file.v.38>Guetter was accused of "improper conduct..., including sexual misconduct" against minors under his care. Family services investigated; no evidence to support criminal charge but did find evidence of general allegations of improper conduct. Guetter filed suits to determine who made the charges. Appeal of lower court's denial was carried to Mn. Supreme Court as of 11/6/87. Have no info on actual charges, if any, filed against Guetter.</file.v.38><file.v.39>Sued May, 2002. Accused of abuse of 1 teenage boy in 1970s. Criminal charges not pursued due to SOL. Reinstated as pastor after 15 months on leave. Diocese could not prove allegations. Another civil suit filed 11/03 and Guichard placed on leave again.Named in total of 4 suits. In Sept. 2006 he filed suits against his accuser and family of a deceased accuser. He filed another suit in Oct. 2006. 5 Plaintiffs have settled claims. Church trial held 11/07.</file.v.39><file.v.40>In lawsuit filed 1/04 , woman claimed that Guiliani forced her to perform seuxal acts from 1971 to 1975 when he was working at Notre Dame High School in 1970s. Also saud he visited her in college in 1975 and asked her to marry him. After her refusal, he never contacted her again. Second woman filed suit 5/04. She alleges that she was sexually molested by Guiliani 12/76 when she was student at Cardinal Brennan High School. He left the priesthod in 1977. Name also spelled GULIANNI AND GIULIANI.</file.v.40><file.v.41>If no upset bids are filed, OR if upset bids are filed and the period for filing additional upset bids has ended with no other upset bids being filed, THEN the foreclosing attorney will contact the high bidder to inform them of the successful bid and to demand the balance of the bid price (or balance of the upset bid price) over and above the initial deposit (or upset bid deposit). These funds must be paid in cash or certified funds to the foreclosing attorney within three (3) days after the demand for the additional funds is made. If a bidder does not honor the bid (or upset bid) by paying in the balance of the additional funds, then that bidder is in default, the bid deposit (or upset bid deposit) will be held pending further orders of the court, and the property will be placed for resale. Remember that, subject to upset bid requirements, all sales are final, absolute, and unconditional - there is no “closing,” settlement statement, financing contingency or any other contingencies. That is why it is so important for bidders to fully check out a property prior to placing any bid or upset bid.</file.v.41><file.v.42>State law provides that any owner, mortgage holder or defendant in a filed tax or assessment foreclosure proceeding can stop the foreclosure process at any time by redeeming the property. The redemption price is equal to the taxes and/or assessments, interest, fees and costs of the foreclosure proceeding to the date of the redemption. Parties wishing to redeem property from tax or assessment foreclosure and stop the foreclosure process must contact the assigned attorney for a redemption payoff figure. Redemption can even occur after a sale, as long as the sale has not been confirmed by the Court. However, once the foreclosure property sale has been completed with a confirmation order and delivery of deed, all rights of redemption are terminated.</file.v.42><file.v.43>(d) Complaint as Lis Pendens.--The complaint in an action brought under this section shall, from the time it is filed in the office of the clerk of superior court, serve as notice of the pendency of the foreclosure action, and every person whose interest in the real property is subsequently acquired or whose interest therein is subsequently registered or recorded shall be bound by all proceedings taken in the foreclosure action after the filing of the complaint in the same manner as if those persons had been made parties to the action. It shall not be necessary to have the complaint cross-indexed as a notice of action pending to have the effect prescribed by this subsection (d).</file.v.43><file.v.44>(e) Subsequent Taxes.--The complaint in a tax foreclosure action brought under this section by a taxing unit shall, in addition to alleging the tax lien on which the action is based, include a general allegation of subsequent taxes which are or may become a lien on the same real property in favor of the plaintiff unit. Thereafter it shall not be necessary to amend the complaint to incorporate the subsequent taxes by specific allegation. In case of redemption before confirmation of the foreclosure sale, the person redeeming shall be required to pay, before the foreclosure action is discontinued, at least all taxes on the real property which have at the time of discontinuance become due to the plaintiff unit, plus penalties, interest, and costs thereon. Immediately prior to judgment ordering sale in a foreclosure action (if there has been no redemption prior to that time), the tax collector or the attorney for the plaintiff unit shall file in the action a certificate setting forth all taxes which are a lien on the real property in favor of the plaintiff unit (other than taxes the amount of which has not been definitely determined).</file.v.44><file.v.45>(g) Special Benefit Assessments.--A cause of action for the foreclosure of the lien of any special benefit assessments may be included in any complaint filed under this section.</file.v.45><file.v.46>The lien of any taxing unit made a party defendant in any foreclosure action shall be alleged in an answer filed by the taxing unit, and the tax collector of each answering unit shall, prior to judgment ordering sale, file a certificate of subsequent taxes similar to that filed by the tax collector of the plaintiff unit, and the taxes of each answering unit shall be of equal dignity with the taxes of the plaintiff unit. Any answering unit may, in case of payment of the plaintiff unit's taxes, continue the foreclosure action until all taxes due to it have been paid, and it shall not be necessary for any answering unit to file a separate foreclosure action or to proceed under G.S. 105-375 with respect to any such taxes.</file.v.46><file.v.47>If a taxing unit properly served as a party defendant in a foreclosure action fails to answer and file the certificate provided for in the preceding paragraph, all of its taxes shall be barred by the judgment of sale except to the extent that the purchase price at the foreclosure sale (after payment of costs and of the liens of all taxing units whose liens are properly alleged by complaint or answer and certificates) may be sufficient to pay such taxes. However, if a defendant taxing unit is plaintiff in another foreclosure action pending against the same property, or if it has begun a proceeding under G.S. 105-375, its answer may allege that fact in lieu of alleging its liens, and the court, in its discretion, may order consolidation of such actions or such other disposition thereof (and such disposition of the costs therein) as it may deem advisable. Any such order may be made by the clerk of the superior court subject to appeal in the same manner as appeals are taken from other orders of the clerk.</file.v.47><file.v.48>Salon manicures are expensive, so any woman on a budget should learn how to give herself a great manicure at home. All you need are a few basic tools you can buy for about the same amount of money you'd spend for a spa manicure. Start by learning the manicuring basics: how to file and shape your fingernails.</file.v.48><file.v.49>File your nails. Use an emery board, metal bar or glass to file your nails. File gently and in one direction at a time. Back-and-forth filing weakens nails and causes them to split.</file.v.49><file.v.50>Shape your nails as you file. While you file the rough edges off your nails, use your file to coax them into the shape you want. Oval nails look pretty on almost all hands and break less easily.</file.v.50><file.v.51>Buff your nails to finish the job. Use a buffer in a back and forth motion to add luster to your nails and get rid of any sharp or ragged edges left over from when you shaped and filed your nails.</file.v.51><file.v.52>A natural nail that has been beautifully filed can make any ones hand look young and elegant. Filing natural nails keeps rough edges from ripping and keeps the nail in a healthy shape. Filing your natural nails should be a critical step to any nail care regimen. So whether you are giving yourself a salon quality manicure or just cutting your nails, do not skip filing them.</file.v.52><file.v.53>Grasp the medium grade emery board in the opposite hand that you will begin filing your natural nails on. Hold the board as you would a pencil to be able to control how you file more gracefully.</file.v.53><file.v.54>Repeat steps 2 to 4 with every natural nail on the hand that you decided to file first. Change the hand that is holding the emery board and repeat steps 2 to 4 with the rest of your natural nails.</file.v.54><file.v.55>Pay close attention when you are filing natural nails. It is very easy to over file natural nails and make them too short.</file.v.55><file.v.56>Do not file natural nails into a squared off nail. This will make them easy to break.</file.v.56><file.v.57>Just remember to always file in one direction, otherwise you'll get jagged results. It's pretty simple once you get the hang of it — and your polish will last longer, too.</file.v.57><file.v.58>I love messing with my nails. I learned a long time ago the correct way to file my nails, and it runs right along with the advice you gave. I use this old glass nail file that I got from a kit years ago and then I use Seacret's Dead Sea Manicure Set, which makes my nails as smooth as glass. Nail polish was one of the best inventions ever 1 Fri, 10/10/2008 - 1:09pm</file.v.58><file.v.59>You can also file your nails to give them a long and oval shape. However, the drawback of such shape is that it is vulnerable to easy breakage and requires lots of preventive measures to avoid splitting and breakage. Thus, you should wisely choose a shape for your nails so that your nails look beautiful and remain strong.</file.v.59><file.v.60>Follow the above given tips to file your nails correctly so that you can flaunt long, healthy, well trimmed and beautiful nails. Along with proper nail filing, you should also follow the basic nail care tips to possess beautiful nails.</file.v.60><file.v.61>I sat down one day, and thought about what I needed to-do to make sure my nails could withstand hard work and immersion in a lot of water. It took me a while, but I finally figured out a way to solve my problem. My nails are over a half inch long, very strong, and still growing. Right now they are too long, too strong and aggravating! It takes me about 30 minutes to file one nail 1/8 th of an inch shorter. I found out that long nails can be a problem in the workplace. During the early days of my experiment, I went ahead and let them grow until I finally, had to cut them off with toe nail clippers, because the length, was potentially hazardous. They are not as long as they originally were because of choice.</file.v.61><file.v.62>Just before I decided to cut them, I went to a manicurist to get them filed because it is too tedious and time consuming for me to-do it. Everyone in the shop were wearing beautiful sculptured nails. When my turn came, the customers glared at my nails, thinking that the artificial nails helped my nails to grow longer. They were mistaken!</file.v.62><file.v.63>When you have completely finished filing both sides of the saw, all the teeth should be nice and uniform. If you filed a rip saw, all the teeth will appear to be the same size. However, if you were filing a crosscut saw, you will notice that the teeth appear to be different sizes. In the partially filed saw at the left, you will notice that the first, third, fifth, seventh and ninth tooth (from the left) all appear to be slightly larger than the tooth to their immediate right. Don't worry, it is merely an illusion caused by the effect of fleam. Since you are looking at the backs of some teeth (non-fleam side) and the fronts of others (fleam side), the teeth appear to be different sizes. However, if you hold it up to the light, you will notice that once you negate the effects of fleam, the teeth are the same size.</file.v.63><file.v.64>Where the toenails are not kept short by being worn down by the dog naturally, they should be cut or filed. The nails are too long when they touch the ground or make a sound when the dog walks on a tiled surface. Filing, with a metal emery board, is recommended should you be nervous about cutting the quick (the blood vessel running through the centre of the nail). Accidentally cutting the quick hurts the dog, and may make him wary of having his nails seen to again. A styptic pencil applied to the affected bleeding quick usually stops the flow of blood quite quickly.</file.v.64><file.v.65>Delicate gardening snips and grass clippers that resemble scissors are best sharpened professionally by a scissors grinder or lawnmower center. Amateurs can file hedge clippers and tree-pruning shears. With either tool, spread the handles wide and brace the tool or clamp it in a vise so that the blade to be sharpened is horizontal. Using a smooth file, stroke across the cutting edge toward the blade. Maintain the original bevel or, if the bevel is not apparent, at an angle of about 60 degrees. Remove as little metal as possible, especially near the tip. On pruning shears that cut against a curved bar, square the bar's edges with the file if they have become rounded. You may need a half-round file to follow the bar's upper contour.</file.v.65><file.v.66>File each nail so that the tip is soft and without rough broken edges. Pet owners appreciate this added touch, and it saves women's stockings! Filing nails that bled may remove the coagulant styptic powder "seal" and resume bleeding. Do not file the seal away. Brittle nails will require more filing to remove burrs.</file.v.66><file.v.67>After the slots are cleaned of debris you can slightly chamfer the top edges of the fret slots by running a triangular needle file along each slot. I'm of mixed opinion as to the value of this. It doesn't seem to be any more difficult to insert the frets one way or the other. If you do this on a bound fingerboard be careful not to file a groove in the binding.</file.v.67><file.v.68>To offset this gradual reduction in cutter height, you must file the depth gauge periodically. Otherwise, the clearance between depth gauge and corner becomes too small, and the chain will not "bite." This is another way chains lose their self-feeding characteristics.</file.v.68><file.v.69>Make sure that you moisturize your nail at the beginning of manicuring to hydrateand nourish your nails to prevent them from flaking when it is filed later on. Regularuse of cuticle oil also will help. Try using gloves while doing household chores.</file.v.69><file.v.70>Blades are much easier to hold firmly between the plates when they are filed before the bevels or Vee grinds are cut. There's just more to hold on to. It also helps to line the "jaws" with a leather pad. Put the leather pads on with rubber cement so they're east to change.</file.v.70><file.v.71>If there is a major gap at the top of a slab handled guard, use the punch technique to tighten it up or just hammer the open top together a bit. You may also use the hammer technique to some degree, to narrow the entire slot if it's been filed too wide, if your hammer is heavy enough, and the guard isn't too wide or thick.</file.v.71><file.v.72>We've filed the guard stub and drilled the pin holes for a 1/8" pin and guard material 3/8" thick. This allows quite a variety of shapes. You only need the top pin hole for the guard. If there are two holes there, the bottom one is just in case you want to change to a bolster.</file.v.72><file.v.73>It’s important that you remove your old polish before opting for a manicure. In manicure, it’s important to file your nails first. File your nails with the help of a filer. Try to file your nails in one particular direction in case of shaping. The best shape in case of nails is filing it in oval shape. After you complete filing of your nails, buff out excess surface of nails. You can take a small bowl, and put warm water, cream and soap into it. Soak your nails in the water for fifteen to twenty minutes. It helps to make your cuticles soft and smooth.</file.v.73><file.v.74>All of the above types of services can be finished with a UV gel top coat to protect the enhancement. The UV coating is applied either with a brush or similar to polish and is "cured" under a UV lamp for around 3 minutes. UV top coats are very protective to the enhancement and will need to be filed off at your next appointment. There might be a slight additional charge for this extra.</file.v.74><file.v.75>To have the fake nails on for a longer time, simply use a nail file and file the surface of your nails. Once your nail surface becomes rigged, apply glue either on your entire finger nail or on half full of the fake nails. Press the fake nails to your actual nails, hold for about 30 seconds and release. If you wish to have the fake nails on for a short amount of time (generally about 1 week or so), you do not need to file your nails. Simply apply glue. For temporary wear (for an event or a night out), you may use professional nail double sided tapes. You may wish to apply a layer of top coat over your fake nails once you have finished the gluing process. Top coat will not only protect your fake nails but also gives a shine to them.</file.v.75><file.v.76>I had to file the edges of the plate on the mic mount slightly. If I recall correctly (this was quite a while ago), there were two tabs on the mic holder that stuck out about a millimeter. I filed those off and it fit. (Go slow; I spent about a half hour on it, filing them down slightly and then checking to see if I'd filed down enough.)</file.v.76><file.v.77>My goal is to be as militent as possible with all of my 2 daily foot soaks, I've filed all the nails, i use gloves for wet work, i bleach all files and nail clippers. I am also not wearing socks hardly ever, and i'm in the rare circumstance that I can wear flip flops all day at work. I also am applying vinegar randomly to fingertips and toes as well as vapo rub. I bleach my socks and lysol my shoes.</file.v.77><file.v.78>Every chain has two sets of cutters, those facing to the right, or right-hand cutters, and those facing to the left, or left-hand cutters. File all the teeth of the cutters on one side, then turn the saw and file all the teeth on the other side. File the cutters evenly on both sides, or your saw will pull to the side instead of cutting downward.</file.v.78><file.v.79>Three Square Files are designed for filing internal angles above 60°, corners, grooves, notches, and for filing HSS taps and cutters after machining. They are double cut on all three sides and taper slightly to point. NOTE: This file has sharp corners and is not recommended for filing saws.</file.v.79><file.v.80>Check the clearance of the rakers (depth gauge), the curved hook shaped links between the cutters. They should clear each cutting edge about one tenth of an inch lower than the cutter. This gauges the amount of chip that the cutter removes on each pass through the wood. A special tool that is laid on top of the blade is available from chainsaw dealers or hardware stores. If the gauge is too high, and must be filed, this tool protects the adjacent tooth as you file the gauge down.</file.v.80><file.v.81>Some 25,000 demonstrators filled the streets of central Paris in the afternoon of Saturday 3 January 2009 in protest against Israel's military action in Gaza. The demonstration was organised by the Collective for a Just Peace between Palestinians and Israelis, which groups left-wing parties, trade unions and Maghrebian (North African) organisations, including a joint Jewish-Maghrebian association. The demonstration filed peacefully through the city until it reached the Place Saint-Augustin, where helmeted, leg-shielded riot police holding perspex shields and side-handled wooden clubs blocked the way. Several hundred young men climbed scaffolding and smashed cars, the police responded with tear gas. The cars were later overturned and some were set on fire.</file.v.81><file.v.82>There were no more threats after the ship left Phu Quo and many soldiers threw rifles, grenades, and other explosives over the side-enough weaponry to convince Iacobacci that the hijackers could certainly have carried out their threat to destroy the vessel. When she landed at Vung Tau the next day, soldiers and other refugees filed peacefully off the ship. Some apologized to the crew as they left. Iacobacci's report even included a bright note. "We also became enriched by three new U.S citizens".</file.v.82><file.v.83>For the increasingly impoverished majority, the rhetoric of concertation is no substitute for reality. They accuse the government of signing and not complying, of proclaiming reconciliation yet promoting conflict, of pretending to work for political stability while implementing anti-worker measures, of insisting that complaints be filed peacefully while ignoring all demands for negotiation and responding only to pressure and threats of violence. For them, concertation should be abandoned because it limits their ability to defend themselves. They view it only as evidence that certain Sandinista tendencies and leaders have "caved in to the bourgeois government."</file.v.83><file.v.84>The fight that has emerged from the health care reform debate came to Montana last week, centered on President Barack Obama’s town hall on Aug. 14 at Gallatin Field Airport near Belgrade. People who want to fix a system they consider broken clashed with angry protesters against health care reform in a field outside the town hall during this rare presidential visit to Montana.At times frenzied, some literally foaming at the mouth, the demonstrators seemed to represent an anomaly among attendees, as those there to see the president speak filed peacefully into the airport hanger, leaving protest signs and chants in the dusty grasslands.</file.v.84><file.v.85>And expensive. In previous raids such as the one in Postville, Iowa ICE spent $5.2 million or about $14,000 per immigrant. Yesterday, no immigrant worker resisted arrest. They filed peacefully onto the bus, their hands and ankles chained. There was a 3:1 ratio of ICE to workers. In this economy, it cannot be a government priority to spend $14,000 per person on a military raid. We ask that the government use its dollars in ways that build up our communities, businesses, and families, not in ways that tears them down.</file.v.85><file.v.86>Among the others arrested were four Swedes, two Germans and nationals from Switzerland, France and Poland and a number of weapons, including baseball bats, were seized. Watched by a heavy police presence, around 500 demonstrators filed peacefully through the city in a second demonstration late on Tuesday after gathering close to the US embassy. "Everybody has the right to protest, to make their voice heard, provided they do so in accordance with the law," said Gianni Alemanno, the mayor of Rome.</file.v.86><file.v.87>In previous raids such as the one in Postville, Iowa ICE spent $5.2 million or about $14,000 per immi­grant. On Tuesday, no immigrant worker resisted arrest. They filed peacefully onto the bus, their hands and ankles chained. In this economy, it cannot be a govern­ment priority to spend $14,000 per person on a military raid. We ask that the government use its dol­lars in ways that build up our communities, businesses, and families, not in ways that tears them down.</file.v.87><file.v.88>Among the others arrested were four Swedes, two Germans and nationals from Switzerland, France and Poland and a number of weapons, including baseball bats, were seized. Watched by a heavy police presence, around 500 demonstators filed peacefully through the city in a second demonstration late Tuesday after gathering close to the United States embassy. 'Everybody has the right to protest, to make their voice heard, provided they do so in accordance with the law,' said Gianni Alemanno, the mayor of Rome. </file.v.88><file.v.89>Croatia also beat Poland 1-0 with a goal from Ivan Klasnic, who has had two kidney transplants in the past 18 months. Croatia, already certain of a place in the quarter-finals before the game, fielded a mainly reserve team but was still too good for the Poles, who were eliminated. Croatia, which finished top of group B with nine points, plays Turkey in the quarter-finals in Vienna on Friday, a day after Germany takes on group A winner Portugal in Basle. In Vienna, referee Manuel Mejuto of Spain ordered coaches Joachim Loew of Germany and Josef Hickersberger of Austria into the stands after a fierce touchline argument before half-time. There was little fan trouble, with a few arrests in Klagenfurt. In Vienna, Austrian fans filed peacefully away from fanzones and public screening areas at the final whistle.</file.v.89><file.v.90>When I got to the store around midnight, some guys were running a bean-bag toss tournament in the street next to the sidewalk, which provided the rest of us with something to do for the next few hours. At 3:00, the BestBuy managers on-duty came out and announced that the door-busters would be allocated by coupons that would be handed out, starting at the head of the line. When the coupons were gone, so was the right to get the item. At 3:45, the managers came back out and began to hand out the coupons and everything remained peaceful and friendly while the process continued. At 5:00, the doors opened and everyone filed peacefully, but quickly into the store.</file.v.90><file.v.91>According to a police spokesman, a total of 36 people, including 27 Italians, were arrested in Rome during the course of the morning. Among the others arrested were four Swedes, two Germans and nationals from Switzerland, France and Poland and a number of weapons, including baseball bats, were seized. Watched by a heavy police presence, around 500 demonstrators filed peacefully through the city in a second demonstration today after gathering close to the United States embassy. "Everybody has the right to protest, to make their voice heard, provided they do so in accordance with the law," said Gianni Alemanno, the mayor of Rome.</file.v.91><file.v.92>As in past years, the celebrations yesterday to mark 52 years since a popular uprising overthrew dictator Gen. Jorge Ubico Casteneda and ushered in democratic rule began with a march through the city's main streets, headed for the central square.  Human rights, campesino and labor organizations called on Guatemalans to help revive the ideals of the revolution that produced the country's first labor code,basic social security and public health care, and an agrarian reform.  And march leaders told onlookers that the accords coming out of the peace negotiations between government and rebel troops will provide the tools for rebuilding the democracy which was crushed in 1954 by a CIA-backed coup. Some 5,000 demonstrators filed peacefully past the national palace and the cordon of Immediate Response Force (FRI) police agents who were in place to prevent access to the building.</file.v.92><file.v.93>"We have waited 15 years, and maybe we have to wait another 15 years." Nine peace doves were released from small cages during the commemoration, which culminated with about 300 of Aung San Suu Kyi's supporters marching to the Shwedagon Pagoda, Burma's most prominent religious site, to offer birthday prayers for their leader. The marchers filed peacefully through the streets of Rangoon, with about a dozen uniformed riot police following in vehicles. With June 19 being observed by opposition groups as Burmese women's day, the NLD's Women Central Committee representatives oversaw the function and spoke out about the appalling conditions in the country. "As far as women are concerned, all we have so far are slogans and nothing else," committee member Leh Leh told the crowd.</file.v.93><file.v.94>It was the middle of the night when Moses led the Israelites out of Egypt. There was little time to pack, and no time to gather extra food for the journey. Thousands and thousands of people filed out, leading goats and sheep, and all they could with them. The Egyptians called out to the Israelites, "Hurry! Hurry! You must leave quickly before we all die!"</file.v.94><file.v.95>Hotdogs for Communism was a installation in Fredonia, NY. As people filed out of a orchestra concert, we gave out free hot dogs amongst the cold grey walls of King Concert Hall. Surrounded by giant video projections displaying short segments of video, the audience was confronted with situation which was both spectacular and absurd.</file.v.95><file.v.96>Last weekend's AIUK  Annual conference was memorable for so many reasons: the debate: the speakers: the hangover ;-) However one of the big many highlights for me was the end. As people filed out of the main conference hall at the end of the day, they passed a small coffee area with a TV screen. It was tuned into the BBC News 24 channel which was relaying a news feed of the Olympic Torch relay through London. As more and more people gathered it was evident that something big was going on. The hushed gathering grew to the point where those at the back could see little of the TV and had to be relayed information from those at the front as to what was going on.</file.v.96><file.v.97>I've just come back in from two minutes stood outside with what felt like the whole of London. At 11.58, we all went outside into the blazing sun, a stark contrast with the wet, chilly air that pervaded the streets of London last Thursday. People were talking, standing, enjoying the sun. Down the street, hundreds upon hundreds of people filed out, from every shop, office block, pub. Busses stopped. Taxis stopped. The pneumatic drills from the roadworks at the end of the road stopped. The fire alarm inside our building sounded, and a wave of silence spread out from the doorway of the office.</file.v.97><file.v.98>Lastly, it's too bad you couldn't have been there in Alaska to tell us what sarah palin was REALLY talking about when she went around "making stuff up." That could have saved us all a lot of hassle. And I'll tell you what, I'll tell you why this infuriates me so much. I work in the health care industry. Last weekend as the wife and kids did some shopping, I went to one of these debates. Unlike most, it was pretty civil. Afterward, I watched as a butt-ton of good, but misguided people filed out of the theater, and immediately lit up a smoke.</file.v.98><file.v.99>"It was a truly inspirational meeting," Mike Schoen, an executive member of Local 35's negotiating committee and a cook for Yale Dining Services, said. "I really think that everyone was quite exhilarated by the event."After listening to the speech, people filed out of the church in two rows. "We let the retirees go first," Schwartz-Weinstein said. "Everybody clapped when they left, which was really powerful." Many supporters of the demonstration had chosen not to be arrested, but were instead official "witnesses" to the event. "You're here as witnesses to tell everyone what you saw," a union leader told them from a stage on the New Haven Green. "So when the newspapers say that there were only 20 people here today, you can tell them how many there really were."</file.v.99><file.v.100>If this was a rock concert, this would be like the encore. Clinton came around the front of the stage after he finished his address to greet people. While most people filed out of the gym, about 100 stood around a barrier waiting to shake hands and snap pictures of the former president. About 10 digitial cameras were being held above the crowd at any one time, and one person near the front of the crowd held up what looked like a copy of Clinton’s memoir.</file.v.100><file.v.101>"If an associate at a law firm had attempted to file these papers, he would have been barred by the clerk, sanctioned by the court, and fired by his firm," observed lead counsel, GW Professor Jonathan Turley. "If these workers are to face such dangers, t hey deserve a full hearing and a motion that demonstrates a modicum of legal attention and care." The court, however, is still considering the merits of the Morgulec filings despite charges that the investigation is a thinly veiled effort of retaliation. </file.v.101><file.v.102>How to file papers that need filing, throw away others. "Organizing my paperwork was a huge weight off my back." How I did it: I sat myself down at my desk when I knew I had some extra time and I didn't leave my desk until every paper was in its place.  Anything that didn't have a place went in the trash.</file.v.102><file.v.103>The compilation of this literature survey was initiated more than a decade ago as a part of science-of-science bibliographies. The collected 150 studies and data sources are concerned with career migration, cross-disciplinary switching, international academic circulation and brain drain of physicists and in physics. The principal criterion for selection of items for listing was that they present fact-finding information on certain enduring aspect of the mobility process. Papers treating more ephemeral approaches are not included but a few conceptual pieces are the exceptions that prove the rule. Most entries are from the published literature. The arrangement of the bibliography is alphabetical by the first author, for each author a chronological order is used. Anonymous and edited works are filed under title. Cross-referencing will facilitate the use. Elementary techniques, such as following up the references in relevant documents, have been applied whenever possible and most documents have been scrutinized by actual reading.</file.v.103><file.v.104>NC-17-Rating: I'm sure you've heard the phrase "X-Rating" before, well, this is exactly the same thing. Graphic sex, including more unusual sex acts, psychologically tormenting violence and bloodshed; basically, everything your mother doesn't want you to be reading. Some of my own works are filed under this rating for bloodshed even if actual intercourse is not present, so this rating doesn't always mean it will be a sex-fest.</file.v.104><file.v.105>Many people, particularly at work, file away all of their email in case they need it for future reference. Others don’t keep everything but of these, many keep the important emails, and perhaps categorize them into Outlook folders. PC-based voice communications and instant messages are just as important as email, and are as worthy of filing away for future reference. However, these are generally lost - i.e. people don’t store them away and archive them as they do with email. This is partly because there are no facilities to allow them to easily do this, or the facilities exist but users are not familiar with them and don’t use them.</file.v.105><file.v.106>This document has been prepared as part of the Policy and Planning (PP) Records Management Project and is aimed primarily at all colleagues working within Policy and Planning. However, it is hoped that the procedures will also be of use to colleagues working in other University units. The procedures are intended to be a quick reference guide to deciding where to file a particular record or set of records.  The procedures are supplemented with a list of frequently asked questions that provide further guidance on specific issues.</file.v.106><file.v.107>The Sent Items Organizer Add-In for Outlook organizes your sent email by implementing three different ways for you to file your sent items. You can file the emails based on who you are sending to, based on keywords that exist in the email subject or body, or have it offer you a chance to save the item to an Outlook folder other than the default. You decide in what order these "rules" run - and if no email meets the requirements to be moved, then it goes into your regular Sent Items folder just like it does now. </file.v.107><file.v.108>Under Actions, select "File the message(s) into the folder SPAM" to automatically file mail marked as spam based on the probability you set into a special folder. Select "Delete the message(s)" to automatically delete any messages marked as spam based on the probability you set. Select the priority level this filter should have. The lower the priority number, the sooner the filter will be executed on a message. </file.v.108><file.v.109>In Outlook 2007, it is possible to create rules to file your messages for you as they are received. In order to create a rule to move any messages marked as spam by the Barracuda: To see a larger version of any of these images, simply click on them. Expand the list of folders for your IMAP account by clicking the "+" next to your account name. </file.v.109></file.v.train>
